Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one, so
let's let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending,
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, it's really
where we should be going, go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride away.
We're all together as well.
So let's escape with a stun.
While our dreams are never ending.
Heartbeat, we will be one of your hands.
My darkness will swallow the world.
Just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow
we will find suspense And then commence
to live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our minds will never give up There's a
fire in our dreams and you can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
Ladies and gents, we have
three of our finalists!
This trio of unbelievable
contestants will now advance
to the final round and challenge
the Don Quixote family.
The champion of Block A, representing
the Blackbeard Pirates, Jesus Burgess!
Our winner from Block B,
the irreverent leader of the pirate
crew called the Baratie Club,
Bartolomeo the Cannibal!
And now from Block C, everyone's
favorite dark horse, Lucy!
The long-anticipated
finale is fast approaching!
Unfortunately,
as the arena needs immediate repairs,
the battle for Block D will be
delayed by about 15 minutes.
Sorry, folks! Oh, come on! Really?
After all that build-up?
We appreciate your patience as
we prepare for the BLOCK D-MATCH!
Straw Hat!
You can't escape this time!
CABBAGE!
Meet the random!
Gavadish doesn't know
when to quit, does he?
I WANT HIM!
What is his deal I don't know
said something about Straw Hat Oh,
you mean Straw Hat isn't
Straw Hat Luffy the one who
couldn't even save his brother's
life during the war the best,
right?
Anybody can get famous for
not being able to do something
Let go me scumbag.
I'll have you know that I happen to be
a nobleman from the kingdom of big shots
I-I can't breathe!
Well, that's funny since you had enough
breath to talk smack a minute ago.
Look here.
The Great Straw Hat Luffy
is a hero in his own time.
He'll be the legend that defines this era!
The future king of the pirates!
I saw it with my own eyes.
It's been over two years since that day.
At lockdown in the East Blue.
On the same scaffold with Gold Roger.
The King of the Pirates was killed.
I heard him shout to the sky?
Wait and see!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
And in that fateful moment
A bolt of thunder split the
heavens and saved his life.
I witnessed a true miracle that day.
Ever since then, I've been following
the Straw Hat's adventures in the news.
Alabasta, Innie's Lobby, Impel Down.
And who could forget that
legendary showdown at Marine Ford?
Hey, boss, what should we do
with the soldiers we captured?
Drown them, I don't care.
Back home, I was just a gang leader
who took over 150 towns. No big deal.
But Luffy inspired me to be great.
So, I set out to sea.
Now, let me see, where were we?
Right, you were making fun of Luffy.
It's just what makes you think
you're anything to write home about,
huh, you jackass?
I was about to cut out your tongue.
Worthless piece of crap!
What the hell is everyone fighting now?
Get your hands off my
sword, I'll kill you!
Can you just leave me alone and let
us settle this crap some other time?
I've been fighting people all day!
Somebody pull him apart! Not me!
I'm staying back!
I don't blame you, pal.
I'm too nervous to walk up to him myself.
And even if I did, what would I say?
Look at that.
He really does have a
scar under his left eye.
He's even more amazing a person.
I can't see through
all these tears of joy.
Who does that cabbage asshole think he is?
I'll rip him limb from
limb and save Luffy.
You're in for it now, Cabin.
Damn it, I'm speechless.
Straw up, Luffy.
There you are.
Don't go anywhere.
Our grandfather has something
important to tell you.
Hang in there, Grandpa. It's okay. Again?
Dude, would you just leave me alone?
I won, okay?
No, listen.
I've abandoned my grudge.
Now I must express my appreciation.
What I wanted to say was thank you.
Wait, grandson of Garf!
You can't escape me!
No way!
Luffy just ran past me! Hold on! Don't go!
How dare you run away from our duel!
The great straw had Luffy in the flesh!
Ooh, I want to talk to him,
but I think I'm too shy!
Please wait for me!
To show my gratitude
for restoring my head,
I'd like to place you in charge
of my grandson's hop-a-swee army.
Stop right there!
Oh, give me a break!
They're all chasing me!
Okay, I'm too tired for all this.
Lucy, this way.
Oh, hey!
You're, uh... I'm Rebecca.
You're in demand, aren't you?
Follow me!
Uh, sure, thanks for the help!
Well then, that goes for Shiro...
Shh!
I guess so.
But I don't think we should
take Aokiji's word for it.
Huh? Oh!
Hey, Captain, I'm sorry! One second!
Straw Hat's here!
Really now?
Put him on!
Hello there!
Blackbeard!
Long time no see, Straw Hat Luffy.
Hey, I know how you feel.
I was surprised to hear you were
my commander's baby brother.
You sure you want to be here?
You're gonna miss the big show.
Don't you want to be there
for your brother's execution?
What do you want?
It's been a while, hasn't it, old friend?
I heard you're competing in
the Gladiator tournament, Lucy.
But forget about the flame flame fruit,
Burgess is going to win that easy.
I wanted Ace to join the Blackbeard Pirates
back in the day, but he turned me down.
So this way, I can have the next
best thing. What do you think?
I'll tell you what I think.
You're never getting Ace's
power as long as I live.
Well, I can't wait to
make you eat those words.
I get the feeling you know each other?
Is that right?
Yeah, kind of.
I can't let him win that prize.
Hey, this is good.
Got any more you can't eat all my
free samples without buying any.
Lucy.
I'm so sorry about that, ma 'am.
Tell me which one you'd like to have Lucy.
Oh Jimmy you're gonna pay for it.
Oh, hello, Rebecca friend of yours
Thanks for your business.
Enjoy it.
Sorry, I couldn't afford to buy you more.
Are you kidding?
Thanks for treating me to lunch, Rebecca.
So where are we?
These are the living quarters for
the gladiators who fight here.
Though I suppose it's more like a prison.
The guest competitors
won't be coming down here.
You can rest up for your next match.
Oh, that's cool. Thanks a lot.
You're such a great fighter.
I was really impressed when
I saw that last battle.
You like it?
The food here is really good.
Oh, hey, you're not hungry too, are you?
I'm so hungry.
Mother, I'm starving.
Oh, I don't get hungry. Ever.
Well, that's weird.
Are you like a samurai or something?
Alright, I got him.
Go for it, Rebecca! Now!
What?
That's why you brought him here, right?
Rebecca!
What is this?
Come on!
Hey, let go of me!
You better not make me drop my food!
Rebecca! Hurry up!
If you don't, you'll never
accomplish your mission!
Wait, what?
Oh, my God.
He actually caught Rebecca.
How did he move faster than her?
Go on, do your worst.
I'll accept my fate, alright?
Wait a minute, you think
I'm gonna hurt you?
But you gave me food!
Yes, but I just tried to kill you!
Well, you tried to attack me, but kill me?
I don't think so.
If he can afford to
forgive her that easily,
that means she was never a
threat to him in the first place.
Don't you think?
What a shame.
This would have been a
good chance to knock out
one of the competitors who
has Devil Fruit powers.
Whoa, mummies!
Oh, come on!
We're prisoners, forced
to fight as gladiators.
So is Rebecca.
They throw us out into
the arena for the crowd's
entertainment to the day
we finally wind up dead.
All because we got on the Don
Quixote family's bad side.
The King promised he would let us go free
if we managed to win a thousand battles.
But no matter how strong you are,
no one can win that many
fights to the death in a row.
And everybody who's tried to run away up
until now has been shot
and killed on sight.
There's no hope left for us now.
Ten years ago,
before Doflamingo became king around here,
we had gladiator matches,
but never to the death.
For all the light there is in this kingdom
of his, there's just as much darkness.
I swear, no matter what it takes,
I will win this competition today.
And with the power of the Flame
Flame Fruit, I kill Doflamingo!
Look,
the toy soldier told me he's planning on
leading his army to
attack Doflamingo today.
That means he's going to let us all out.
I believe that he can save this kingdom.
But he wants to sacrifice
his life to do it.
It's all right.
Don't be afraid.
This brave soldier will
always be at your side.
But I will settle this
before he has the chance.
I'm sick of him always
having to protect me.
This time, soldier, I'll
protect you. I promise.
He won't make it this time!
He'll die!
Who are you talking about?
He's a toy soldier with only one leg.
A toy—may I offer to carry
your belongings for you?
You know, I met someone like
that in front of the coliseum.
Yeah, it was probably him.
We're not allowed to step
foot outside the arena,
even if we wanted to help your friend.
There's nothing we can do in here.
I mean, is it possible
for a toy to be killed,
and being alive in the first
place still seems weird?
You're not from around here, so
it's difficult to understand.
They aren't any different
from us humans—whether
it's being friends for
the friendless siblings,
for those without family, or
bringing love to the lonely.
I don't understand why it's against
the law for them to live with us.
You know, ever since the day I...
day I When I lost my mother, I
didn't have any family of my own.
He brought me up like
I was his own daughter.
I don't think of him as a toy.
He's more like a father to me.
Wow, you two sound really close.
Thank you for your patience, the
ring has been fully repaired.
Rebecca, the match is about to start.
Lucy, are you eating food off the ground?
When we were wrestling earlier, two
of the lunches fell on the floor, see?
You spent hard-earned money on them.
I didn't want them to go to waste.
Besides, they still taste good.
You know, you don't look like a prisoner.
The tournament's resuming.
Old Block D contestants to the rings!
Hey, Mother!
Mother, look at all the flowers I found.
There's so many of them.
I picked this one just for you.
It's beautiful.
Thank you, Rebecca.
And this is from your mother to you.
Right, let's go. Yeah.
We did good selling all the flowers today.
I say we dig in.
That sounds like a great idea.
You must be starving
from all your hard work.
Yep, I was getting so hungry, my
stomach wouldn't stop growling. Oh, no.
This is really yummy. Good.
It goes out!
He's burning the bellens!
Make them stop!
It doesn't make any sense.
Why is the king doing this?
That's the royal palace.
It's on fire.
Why is this happening?
Our country's falling apart.
Run, lady scarlet!
I'll hold him back.
Who's the short? Shoot him! Run!
Don't look back!
i'm so hungry mother i'm starving i know
dear two days is a long time to wait
you'll have to stay here alone for a while
okay rebecca you promise me you won't
leave this spot no matter what i'm going
to bring us something to eat Really?
Is that you, mother?
I...
I couldn't save her.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
She told me to give you this food,
but you were waiting here
patiently for her to return.
I'm so hungry.
Mother, I'm starving.
I'm going to bring us something to eat.
Mother!
Please, Mother!
The trail of blood leads over this way!
They gotta be around here somewhere close.
Keep looking!
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You have to eat.
Well, if you don't, I'll just
eat it myself. Here I go.
I'm about to chew up all this food.
Your mother was highborn.
She was a very special woman.
These are dangerous times.
Did you know we have a new king now?
This new ruler.
His mission is to capture anyone who
is related to the former nobility.
And because you have your mother's
blood, he'll be coming for you too.
I regret I couldn't
save your mother's life.
But I will devote mine to
protect yours, whatever the cost.
Someday, happiness will return to you.
Until then, I will stay by your side.
I'd rather have my mother!
I hate you, because you couldn't save her!
I hate you!
Well, how about now?
How could you hate this?
What if I spin around?
Wait, where are you going, Rebecca?
I'm going back home!
You can't.
It isn't safe there.
The new king has people watching
the village and your old house.
Let's hear it for a moment!
Go, go, go, go!
The Rick dynasty has presided over this
land of misery and poverty for centuries.
In the end,
they even sank to stealing valuables from
their citizens in an
act of shameless greed.
But me?
I'm going to make this
country wealthy instead.
I guess toys do know how to work.
Try to earn a living.
Rebecca!
YAAA!
YAAA! YAAA! YAAA!
No use!
I'm unbreakable!
No matter what happens, I will never stop!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
This toy soldier is brave and true.
In the rain or in the snow,
he will stay with you.
It must be cold for her.
Not that I would know.
This tin body feels nothing.
is that better yes your hand is very warm
this toy soldier is brave and true in the
rain or in the snow he will stay with you
how much he's lodging you can
stay in one of the empty houses
for free people lived here before
Poor King Rick burned the town,
but most of them have moved away.
It's so warm inside.
You should close the window.
No way!
Looks like there's a
bunch of toys living here.
And other children too.
You should go play.
But since there are other people in the
village, we'll have to follow the law.
After you've gone to sleep, I'll
go back to the house of toys.
But I'll return before you wake up.
To let you know I'm around,
I'll drop a flower petal through the
crack in the window every morning.
Good morning, soldier, sir! Indeed!
It is a ralph!
You little monkey!
Super cool!
Does this warrant a bonus?
A very happy birthday to you, Rebecca!
Read this!
My...
my poor heart!
She must be an orphan.
Which means no family's gonna miss her.
Rebecca!
Seems we hit the jackpot.
Kaido like her will fetch us a good price.
They're taking her.
Whoa!
Little bastard, you think a human
will lose to some crappy toy?
I'm gonna break you!
No, Dad, no!
I'll save you!
Sorry, but I'm on the wanted list now.
So am I.
We'll find a new home.
You know, I wish we could both actually
live in the same house one day.
You're going to learn to defend yourself.
What for?
I mean, I've got you.
And what if something should happen to me?
Now fight!
My mother told me I should never
hurt others, no matter what.
But you must protect yourself
from those who would hurt you.
Come on!
He's always been at my side.
Saved my life countless times.
And here she comes!
The most beautiful gladiator in the
Colosseum, the infamous phantom princess,
no other fighter could possibly
rile up the crowd more than her!
My soldier, please don't die.
You never gave up.
So neither will I.
I'm going to die this time.
No!
Get her!
Go to pieces!
What the hell?
I don't get why everyone
hates her so much. Screw her.
She's a really nice person.
I mean, hey, she even bought me too much.
It doesn't matter.
She's bound by her family's legacy.
Her grandfather was our former king.
The entire country despises him.